<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on WELCOME</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on WELCOME</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests  Computer architecture Processor design: Performance and security  About &amp;ensp;&amp;ensp;&amp;ensp; I am an Associate Researcher at the State Key Laboratory of Information Security, Institute of Information Engineering, Chinese Academy of Sciences. I earned a PhD degree in Institute of Information Engineering, Chinese Academy of Sciences in 2021, where I worked with Professor Rui Hou. I received the ME degree from the School of Electronic Engineering, University Of Electronic Science and Technology of China in 2017 and the BE degree from the School of Electrical Engineering and Automation, Henan Polytechnic University in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honors</title>
      <link>/home/honors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/honors/</guid>
      <description> APPT 2021 Best Paper Award IEEE TC Feature Paper of the Month: July 2021  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/experience/</guid>
      <description>2021.8-Present, Institute of Information Engineering, Chinese Academy of Sciences
 Location: No Jia 89, Minzhuang Road, Haidian District, Beijing Title: Associate Researcher Duties: Participate in the development of active security processor  2017.9-2021.7, Institute of Information Engineering, Chinese Academy of Sciences
 PhD degree Major in Processor Architecture and Security  2014.9-2017.7, School of Electronic Engineering, University Of Electronic Science and Technology of China
 ME degree Major in Circuit and System  2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>✉️ zhaolutan@iie.ac.cn
-- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/academic/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>