<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on WELCOME</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on WELCOME</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests  Computer architecture Processor design: Performance and security Data center server architecture AI security  About &amp;ensp;&amp;ensp;&amp;ensp;Dr. Rui Hou’s major research interest includes CPU architecture and security, as well as data center server design. Before joined IIE, he was a professor of Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences. He published over 30 papers in international conferences and journals, and got more than 50 patents. Rui has also served more than ten times on conference organizing committees in international academia community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honors</title>
      <link>/home/honors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/honors/</guid>
      <description> National Science Foundation of China for Excellent Young Scholars, China, 2015  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Services</title>
      <link>/home/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/academic/</guid>
      <description> Journal of Parallel and Distributed Computing, Associate Editor MICRO 2021, TPC MICRO 2020, TPC HPCA 2019, TPC HPCA 2018, TPC PACT 2018, TPC ISPASS 2019 TPC Euro-par 2014, TPC Program Co-Chair, Computing Frontier 2015 Micro 2018, Publicity co-chair HPCA 2013, Web Chair PPoPP 2013, Local Chair Organizer, EDCS (Efficient Data Center System), 2012-2015, co-held with HPCA and ISCA Organizer, Built-in security workshop, co-held with CCS 2018 and HPCA 2019 Member of Computer Architecture，CCF  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/experience/</guid>
      <description>2017.3-Present, Institute of Information Engineering, Chinese Academy of Sciences  Location: No Jia 89, Minzhuang Road, Haidian District, Beijing Title: Professor Duties: Lead the Built-in security team, which focus on the architecture &amp;amp; micro-architecture security mechanisms  2011.3-2017.2, Institute of Computing Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences  Location: No 6, Kexueyuan south road, Haidian District, Beijing Title: Professor (2011.3-2015.8, Associate Professor, 2015.9-2017.2, Professor) Duties: Lead the cpu team which proposed the cost-effective data center server architecture and developed related workload processing unit (WPU, which is new SoC processor chip integrating light-weighted resource sharing protocol and self-developed ARMv8 processor core)  2007.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>